Header

tagline: We're getting married!
headline: Anne & Luke
date: July 1, 2018

Locations

ceremony: Matthias Church, 2 Trinity Square, Budapest
photos: Liberty Bastion, Trinity Square, Budapest
party: Liberty Bastion Restaurant, 1-2 Andrew Hess Square, Budapest

Program

tagline: "It's going to be somehow, that's for sure."
times:
  13:45 – Wedding ceremony
  14:30 – Photos
  16:00 – Cocktails
  18:00 – Dinner
  22:00 – Cake
  ... - 4:00 – Dance until dawn

Gifts:

tagline: The greatest gift for us is to have you there.
paragraph: Please, just bring yourself and have fun with us.

Questions and Answers

travel and accomodations:

  Will there be some kind of organized transfer?
  No, we'll just meet at the church at 13:15.

  Where can I park?
  Parking is free on the weekends in the 1st district. The locations are close to each other so you won't need your car.

  How can I get home at night?
  The 916 bus is in service all night at the castle and it hits every major traffic hub in the city.

food and festivities:

  I'd like to do some kind of surprise for you guys at the party. To whom should I talk about this?
  Discuss it with Abigail Smith. Just drop her an email at abigail@awesomemail.com.

  What should I wear? Do you have a dress code?
  Wear what's comfortable to you. If it helps smart casual / business casual for the ladies and smart casual / informal for the gentlemen are perfect options.

  I would like some kind of special food (gluten-free, lactose-free, vegan etc.)
  Drop us a line here and we'll find a way.

other small stuff:

  I have a problem / question on the wedding day. With whom can I speak?
  Jared Wright on this number: +36 30 000 0000.

  Can we bring kids?
  Sure! We planned a whole toy / sweets corner for them.

  How do you feel about dogs? Can I bring mine?
  We love dogs and you can absolutely bring yours. The Heaven Lounge is a dog-friendly place.

Contact

paragraph: If you have any questions feel free to call / write us.
phone (Anne): +36 30 000 0000
phone (Luke): +36 30 000 0000
email: anneandluke@awesomemail.com

Footer

paragraph: Made with ♥ in Budapest ©2018 | Icons by Becris (CC 3.0 BY)
link to artist: http://www.flaticon.com/authors/becris
link to license: https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/